surflinegh.com 2016-11-22

# Surfline - Privacy Policy

**SURFLINE COMMUNICATIONS LIMITED  **

This Privacy Policy explains SURFLINE’s treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to all SURFLINE website referencing this Privacy Policy (the "Surfline Site") and all services made available on the SURFLINE Site (collectively, unless noted otherwise, the "Surfline Services"). SURFLINE acknowledges and respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites which are not owned or controlled by SURFLINE. We advise that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and check periodically as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED  **

In the course of operating the SURFLINE Services, we may collect two types of information about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. 

"Personal Information" is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender and/or your company contact information. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a SURFLINE Service you choose to subscribe to, when you enter a SURFLINE promotion or choose to receive a SURFLINE newsletter. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information. We will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member's account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, email address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information. 

"Non-Personal Information" is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain you may have used to access a SURFLINE Service, the type and version of browser or operating system you may be using, and the website you may have come from and visit next. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a SURFLINE Service, is also considered Non-Personal Information. 

SURFLINE derives or collects and uses Non-Personal Information in the course of operating the SURFLINE Services. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie or through a Web Beacon when you choose to visit a SURFLINE Service. 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  **

Personal Information may be used by SURFLINE for the following purposes: 

Providing you with the SURFLINE Services and information you have requested from us, including your use of the SURFLINE Site. SURFLINE may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to the SURFLINE Services;  

If you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from SURFLINE or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, SURFLINE may send you emailed materials and other mailings about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If at any time you would like to end your subscription to any such email materials, you will be required to follow the links posted in the outbound emails; 

If you enter a contest or other promotion offered on a SURFLINE Site, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion;  

SURFLINE, if it has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial or foreign law or in order to protect or defend a legal interest, may also use Personal Information. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  **

SURFLINE will not sell or rent out your Personal Information to any third parties. 

SURFLINE will only disclose your Personal Information to third parties under the following reasons: 

  * Where you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your Personal Information for a designated purpose; 
  * Third parties are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers or service providers, solely to enable us to more efficiently provide you with the SURFLINE Services. Such entities act under strict contractual controls, requiring them to maintain the confidentiality of all such Personal Information and to use such information solely for purposes related to the provision of the SURFLINE Services; 
  * To facilitate the provision of such SURFLINE Service, such as fulfilling legal requirements, as may be set out in the Terms and Conditions applicable to a SURFLINE Service; 
  * To compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest as required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority; or 
  * In connection with a SURFLINE corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of SURFLINE provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

A SURFLINE Service may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that SURFLINE is not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the SURFLINE Services referencing this Privacy Policy. 

The majority of the advertisements which are displayed in connection with the SURFLINE Services are served through reputable third party advertisement serving partner(s). 

**SECURITY**  

The security of your Personal Information is important to SURFLINE. SURFLINE takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your Personal Information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business. 

In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card information to us, SURFLINE works to help protect the security of your credit card information during transmission by using industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. 

You can help protect the security of your Personal Information as well by taking certain simple precautions:  never give out your password, since this is what is used to access your Account or Registration Information. Also remember to log out of your account and close your browser window after using a SURFLINE Service or surfing the Web, thereby preventing other users of computer from gaining access to your information. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  **

As new SURFLINE Services are introduced and added or old ones changed, SURFLINE may from time to time make changes to its Privacy Policy. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted at a SURFLINE Site. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates by checking the date of "Last Update" at the top of this document. 

**ADDITIONAL PRIVACY PROCEDURES  **

Privacy procedures specific to a SURFLINE Service can be found on a SURFLINE Site at the location of the particular SURFLINE Service, or in additional terms referenced at such SURFLINE Site. Those procedures are an addendum to this policy and are provided to you at the place where they will be of most use to you. 

**ACCESSING AND CHANGING ACCOUNT/ REGISTRATION INFORMATION  **

SURFLINE provides you with the means to access and update some of your Registration Information you may have provided to us at any time on your own by going to the appropriate page on the MySurfline Portal. 

If you are unsure whether we have a record containing any of your Personal Information and would like to confirm whether or not we do, please Contact Us, indicating all e-mail addresses that you may have given us. 

If you decide at any time that you do not want to receive any e-mail materials to which you have subscribed, you may choose to unsubscribe to these e-mails by following the links posted in the outbound emails.

**LIMITATION AND LIABILITY**

You expressly understand and agree that in no event shall SURFLINE, including its affiliates and licensors, be liable for any damages whatsoever, including any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, special or exemplary damages, and any damages for loss of profits, savings, goodwill or other intangible losses, regardless of whether SURFLINE had been advised of or could have foreseen the possibility of such damages, arising out of or in connection with: (a) the use, inability to use or performance of any of the services of SURFLINE site, or (b) any unauthorized access to or modification to any of your content or transmissions, or (c) any other matter relating to SURFLINE site or any of the services. 

**QUESTIONS, COMMENTS OR SUGGESTIONS**

If you have questions, comments or suggestions about this Privacy Policy or SURFLINE's privacy practices that were not answered in this document, Contact Us 

© 2011 SURFLINE Communications Limited. All Rights Reserved.
